[Documentation
    
    Usage instructions and reference](https://docs.startbootstrap.com/sb-ui-kit-pro/quickstart)
    
    [Components
    
    Code snippets and reference](https://docs.startbootstrap.com/sb-ui-kit-pro/components)
    
    [Changelog
    
    Updates and changes](https://docs.startbootstrap.com/sb-ui-kit-pro/changelog)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: August 2021

Our service can exist only if our customers can be sure that their data is safe. Thus, privacy is of the highest priority for us. We will explain in more detail how Convertr handles your data.

* * *

1\. Personal Data We Collect
----------------------------

By visiting our website and/or using our API, your IP address will be logged, along with the HTTP referrer, the user agent, and the dates of access (log data).

We do not read or collect file content, metadata, or other data from your uploaded files. For statistical purposes, we collect only the number of converted files, the number of errors, and the total file size of all your conversions.

* * *

2\. Use of Your Personal Data
-----------------------------

We log your IP address to prevent abuse of our service and for broad demographic analysis. We do not link this information to any personally identifiable information.

* * *

3\. Handling of Your Files
--------------------------

In the course of providing the service, your files are transferred to and temporarily stored on Convertr servers. We do not read, look into, or mine any data from your files or their metadata, and we do not make any copies of them. All file processing is done by machine; there is no human interaction with your files. Your files are irreversibly deleted from our servers within 24 hours.

* * *

4\. Sharing Your Data
---------------------

Your uploaded files will not be given out or sold to anyone. Assuming you did not provide the download link, no one will ever have access to your uploaded or converted files.

* * *

5\. Keeping your Data
---------------------

We will keep your personal data for as long as it is necessary to provide you with our services. Your files are deleted immediately and irreversible from our servers when use the delete button. This will happen automatically at the latest after 24 hours.

All log data (IP address, user agent, referrer) is deleted after 14 days.

* * *

6\. Security
------------

We are committed to protecting your personal data and your files. Convertr takes all necessary measures to keep your personal information and your files private and secure. The Convertr staff is trained to properly handle your data. All third-party employees who have access to your personal information have signed data processing agreements.

Convertr maintains a secure IT environment, and all security measures are constantly adjusted to technical progress. All transfers from and to Convertr are SSL encrypted. All Convertr servers are located in the European Union and are equipped with appropriate measures to prevent unauthorized access (i.e., hacking). To explain our security measurements in detail would be too lengthy for this page; if you want more details about our security practices, please read our Security Overview and feel free to contact us.

* * *

7\. Cookies
-----------

Convertr stores so-called cookies to be able to offer you a comprehensive range of functions and to make it easier for you to use our websites. Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer with the help of the internet browser. If you do not want to use cookies, you can prevent them from being stored on your computer by using the corresponding settings on your internet browser. Please note that this action may restrict the functional capability and the range of functions of our offer.

* * *

8\. Analytics
-------------

We use Google Analytics to store information about how visitors use our website so that we can make improvements and give visitors a better user experience. Google Analytics is a third-party information storage system by Google that records information about the pages you visit, the length of time you were on specific pages and the website in general, how you arrived at the site, and what you clicked on. You can opt out of Google Analytics on this and all other websites using a browser plugin.

* * *

We're here to help
------------------

Convertr.org

Convert your Audio, Video and other Files from one format to another online for free!

Conversions

About

Legal

* * *

Copyright © Convertr.org 2020 - 2024

[Privacy Policy](https://convertr.org/privacy) · [Terms and Conditions](https://convertr.org/terms)
